the sum of the powers of one-fifth is
one-fourth but why is that well consider
a square whose set length is one and
connect each vertex to the midpoint of
the following Edge like this the Central
Square will have an area of one-fifth
because look I can build five identical
squares and therefore also this red
triangle we have an area of one-fifth
and I can repeat the process in the
Central Square like this and I'll get a
new red triangle whose area is one-fifth
times one-fifth that is one over five
squared and I can keep repeating the
process like this till I get this shape
that fits four times in the Square
and therefore